module.exports = [
	{
		question: 'What is the \'birdie\' in the game of badminton also known as?',
		a: 'Shuttlecock',
		b: 'Dart',
		c: 'Toypedo',
		d: 'Arrow',
		answer: 'a'
	},
	{
		question: 'What type of beverage is associated with a sommelier?',
		a: 'Ale',
		b: 'Tequila',
		c: 'Lager',
		d: 'Wine',
		answer: 'd'
	},
	{
		question: 'Which of the following is not one of the Seven Deadly Sins?',
		a: 'Pride',
		b: 'Rage',
		c: 'Lust',
		d: 'Avarice',
		answer: 'b'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who is known as \'The Friendly Ghost\'?',
		a: 'Boo',
		b: 'Slimer',
		c: 'Casper',
		d: 'Beetlejuice',
		answer: 'c'
	},
	{
		question: 'What company originated the catchphrase \'Where\'s the beef?\'?',
		a: 'Purdue',
		b: 'Arby\'s',
		c: 'Oscar Mayer',
		d: 'Wendy\'s',
		answer: 'd'
	},
	{
		question: 'The kneecap is also known as what?',
		a: 'Tibia',
		b: 'Patella',
		c: 'Sphenoid',
		d: 'Clavicle',
		answer: 'b'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who invented the modern toilet?',
		a: 'Sir John Harington',
		b: 'Thomas Edison',
		c: 'Emmett Lathrop Brown',
		d: 'Sir Henry Cole',
		answer: 'a'
	},
	{
		question: 'What kind of weapon is a falchion?',
		a: 'Sword',
		b: 'Axe',
		c: 'Bow',
		d: 'Gun',
		answer: 'a'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was Mickey Mouse\'s original name?',
		a: 'Mortimer Mouse',
		b: 'Mankey Mouse',
		c: 'Mighty Mouse',
		d: 'Mr. Mouse',
		answer: 'a'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who invented the cotton gin in 1793?',
		a: 'Atticus Finch',
		b: 'Eli Whitney',
		c: 'Wright Brothers',
		d: 'Steve Smobs',
		answer: 'b'
	},
];